export const chapter = "Chapter - 18: The United Nations  ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "What is the main goal of the United Nations?",
        optionA: "Promoting economic growth",
        optionB: "Maintaining international peace and security",
        optionC: "Expanding military power",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "How many countries signed the UN Charter to establish the United Nations in 1945?",
        optionA: "50",
        optionB: "51",
        optionC: "193",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What was the purpose of forming the League of Nations in 1920?",
        optionA: "To establish world peace",
        optionB: "To prevent wars",
        optionC: "To foster worldwide cooperation",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What significant event led to the formation of the United Nations in 1945?",
        optionA: "The First World War",
        optionB: "The Second World War",
        optionC: "The League of Nations' success",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "When was the Universal Declaration of Human Rights adopted by the United Nations?",
        optionA: "1914",
        optionB: "1939",
        optionC: "1948",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following is NOT one of the rights granted by the Universal Declaration of Human Rights?",
        optionA: "Right to travel anywhere in the world",
        optionB: "Right to equal compensation for equal work by men and women",
        optionC: "Right to own property",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the significance of the olive branches on the UN flag?",
        optionA: "Symbol of unity",
        optionB: "Symbol of peace",
        optionC: "Symbol of prosperity",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "How many official languages does the United Nations have for inter-government meetings and documents?",
        optionA: "Two",
        optionB: "Four",
        optionC: "Six",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What has been the most important achievement of the United Nations?",
        optionA: "Promoting technological advancement",
        optionB: "Preventing a Third World War",
        optionC: "Expanding its military power",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question: "What do UN peacekeeping forces aim to do in conflict zones?",
        optionA: "Promote economic growth",
        optionB: "Maintain international peace and security",
        optionC: "Expand their military presence",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "The United Nations is the world's platform to build understanding between nations, find ways to co-operate, and launch coordinated action on problems that transcend borders, from _______ to climate change to pandemics.",
        options: ["hunger", "terrorism", "education"],
        correctAnswer: "terrorism",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The United Nations is an organization that includes almost all the world's countries or nations (__________).",
        options: ["195", "193", "51"],
        correctAnswer: "193",
      },
      {
        question: "The main goal of the United Nations is _______.",
        options: [
          "promoting economic growth",
          "maintaining international peace and security",
          "expanding military power",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "maintaining international peace and security",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The United Nations also works to reduce poverty and suffering and to improve people's lives in other ways. It tries to find peaceful solutions to disagreements between countries. If fighting breaks out, the United Nations sometimes sends in military troops to try to _______ it.",
        options: ["start", "stop", "escalate"],
        correctAnswer: "stop",
      },
      {
        question:
          "After a war, UN organizations provide money to help countries _______.",
        options: ["start new wars", "rebuild", "expand their territories"],
        correctAnswer: "rebuild",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The United Nations also tries to protect human rights and makes sure that everyone gets equal treatment regardless of _______, sex, language, or religion.",
        options: ["nationality", "race", "income"],
        correctAnswer: "race",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Some wars have been very terrible, one such war was the First World War (1914-18). In it, many countries of the world participated and suffered immensely in terms of life and _______.",
        options: ["peace", "prosperity", "property"],
        correctAnswer: "property",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The idea behind founding this organization was noble, but there were some shortcomings in it. Moreover, the world situation was very explosive at that time. This organization could not prevent the dreaded Second World War from occurring just _______ years later.",
        options: ["20", "50", "100"],
        correctAnswer: "20",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Second World War started in 1939 and lasted until 1945. It claimed _______ lives.",
        options: ["1.6 crore", "5 crore", "10 crore"],
        correctAnswer: "5 crore",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The United Nations adopted the Universal Declaration of Human Rights on 10 December, 1948. This day is observed as Human Rights Day all over the world. It has given the following rights to all human beings: Right to live as free citizens, right to equality before the law, right to freedom of _______.",
        options: ["travel", "thoughts", "work"],
        correctAnswer: "thoughts",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "The United Nations is an organization that includes almost all the world's countries or nations (193).",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "The main goal of the United Nations is world peace.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The League of Nations was able to prevent the Second World War from occurring.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The United Nations adopted the Universal Declaration of Human Rights on 10 December, 1948.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The UN flag consists of a map of the world viewed from the South Pole.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The United Nations has six official languages used in inter-government meetings and documents.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The United Nations has successfully prevented a possible Third World War.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "UN peacekeeping forces aim to escalate conflicts in war-torn regions.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "Tamil Nadu is bounded by the Bay of Bengal to the west.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The United Nations promotes economic growth as its primary objective.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
